Guide to the Andrew Smith Gallery Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2014 Acquisition
  - Electronic media, Series IX
    - Electronic media, 2000-2010
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0835; 1 (Box 654)
      - WEEK 3-2, 2014-wa-16-0836; 1 (Box 654)
      - WEEK 2-2, 2014-wa-16-0837; 1 (Box 654)
      - GORDON'S PHOTOGRAPHY PRICES 2001-1970 V. 4.0 "Electronic Book", 2014-wa-16-0838; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 03, 2014-wa-16-0839; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 02, 2014-wa-16-0840; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 03, 2014-wa-16-0841; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 02, 2014-wa-16-0842; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 03, 2014-wa-16-0843; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 01, 2014-wa-16-0844; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 01, 2014-wa-16-0845; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 01, 2014-wa-16-0846; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 02, 2014-wa-16-0847; 1 (Box 654)
      - Peter Hammond, 2014-wa-16-0849; 1 (Box 654)
      - GORDON'S PHOTOGRAPHY PRICES 2001-1970 v. 3.1 "Electronic Book", 2014-wa-16-0850; 1 (Box 654)
      - GORDON'S PHOTOGRAPHY PRICES 2001-1970 v. 3.3 "Electronic Book", 2014-wa-16-0851; 1 (Box 654)
      - JACK SPENCER APARICIONES DISC 1 CONTACT SHEETS, 2014-wa-16-0852; 1 (Box 654)
      - JACK SPENCER 'APARICIONES' DISC 2 CONTACT SHEETS, 2014-wa-16-0853; 1 (Box 654)
      - 6-2, 2014-wa-16-0854; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0855; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0856; 1 (Box 654)
      - 8-2, 2014-wa-16-0857; 1 (Box 654)
      - BACK UP 4/11/03, 2014-wa-16-0858; 1 (Box 654)
      - WINDOWS THROUGH THE CURTAIN DAVID HLYNSKY, 2014-wa-16-0859; 1 (Box 654)
      - Gerald Stiebel Photos, 2014-wa-16-0860; 1 (Box 654)
      - 19th Century Photos of the American West R. G. Lewis 10-24-01, 2014-wa-16-0861; 1 (Box 654)
      - WS/1054 After Conservation, 2014-wa-16-0862; 1 (Box 654)
      - Emerson Scans 03 05/24/01, 2014-wa-16-0863; 1 (Box 654)
      - Emerson Scans 02 5/24/01, 2014-wa-16-0864; 1 (Box 654)
      - Emerson Scans 01 5/24/01, 2014-wa-16-0865; 1 (Box 654)
      - Static Webpage Files 12/09/03, 2014-wa-16-0866; 1 (Box 654)
      - David Michael Kennedy Landscapes, Large Clouds, State Pen, Nudes, 2014-wa-16-0867; 1 (Box 654)
      - Vroman Diary - 1897, 2014-wa-16-0868; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0869; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data 01 05/23/01, 2014-wa-16-0870; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0871; 1 (Box 654)
      - Danny Lyon Indian Nations Part One, 2014-wa-16-0872; 1 (Box 654)
      - Curtis set, 2014-wa-16-0873; 1 (Box 654)
      - TRAGALUZ PHOTOGRAPHS BY BILL WITTLIFF 1997-2004, 2014-wa-16-0874; 1 (Box 654)
      - AA/1466, 2014-wa-16-0875; 1 (Box 654)
      - 5/10/05 Adobe Photoshop CS2 10450235389243122841, 2014-wa-16-0876; 1 (Box 654)
      - Austin's work for Andy. Andy's Copy, 2014-wa-16-0877; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0878; 1 (Box 654)
      - new images mostly Dec. 28, 2004 13 images (c) 2004 BARBARA Van Cleve sized to approximately 4x6, 2014-wa-16-0879; 1 (Box 654)
      - Kashmir 2006, 2014-wa-16-0880; 1 (Box 654)
      - The David C. and Sarajean Ruttenberg Arts Foundation Collection presented by: Stephen Daiter Gallery, 2014-wa-16-0881; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0882; 1 (Box 654)
      - anjozianart.com 949 378 5239, 2014-wa-16-0883; 1 (Box 654)
      - FHM - 1041, 2014-wa-16-0884; 1 (Box 654)
      - WOUNDED KNEE, 2014-wa-16-0885; 1 (Box 654)
      - Backup Artists F-K, 2014-wa-16-0886; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0887; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0888; 1 (Box 654)
      - Backup Artists A-E, 2014-wa-16-0889; 1 (Box 654)
      - Joan Myers 982-9410, 2014-wa-16-0890; 1 (Box 654)
      - Joan Myers 982-9410, 2014-wa-16-0891; 1 (Box 654)
      - Joan Myers 982-9410, 2014-wa-16-0892; 1 (Box 654)
      - Joan Myers 982-9410, 2014-wa-16-0893; 1 (Box 654)
      - BARON WOLMAN'S DISC, 2014-wa-16-0894; 1 (Box 654)
      - Volakis, Emanuel Garden series Sculpture series, 2014-wa-16-0895; 1 (Box 654)
      - Flor Garduño InnerLight/Witness of Time, 2014-wa-16-0896; 1 (Box 654)
      - 4-1, 2014-wa-16-0897; 1 (Box 654)
      - 1-1, 2014-wa-16-0898; 1 (Box 654)
      - Jody SW Brochure, 2014-wa-16-0899; 1 (Box 654)
      - GORDON'S PHOTOGRAPHY PRICES 2002-1970 v. 5.0 "ELECTRONIC BOOK", 2014-wa-16-0900; 1 (Box 654)
      - SBM-1001, 2014-wa-16-0901; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 03, 2014-wa-16-0902; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA-1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 02 Disc 01, 2014-wa-16-0903; 1 (Box 654)
      - Andy's Prints 05/18/01, 2014-wa-16-0904; 1 (Box 654)
      - Parkhurst 02/21/02, 2014-wa-16-0905; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data 03 01/30/02, 2014-wa-16-0906; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data 02 11/23/01, 2014-wa-16-0907; 1 (Box 654)
      - 5-1, 2014-wa-16-0908; 1 (Box 654)
      - 6-1, 2014-wa-16-0909; 1 (Box 654)
      - HUMANITAS 72 DPI c. 2005 FREDRIC ROBERTS, 2014-wa-16-0910; 1 (Box 654)
      - PATRICK NAGATANI (20) "CHROMATHERAPY" IMAGES 300dpi jpg's, 2014-wa-16-0911; 1 (Box 654)
      - ANSEL ADAMS POINTS OF VIEW, 2014-wa-16-0912; 1 (Box 654)
      - xhibition Prints July 21 2006 To ASMITH Gallery, 2014-wa-16-0913; 1 (Box 654)
      - Zig's final pic's Zig JACKSON IMAGES, 2014-wa-16-0914; 1 (Box 654)
      - Tiff's - Indian Albums, 2014-wa-16-0915; 1 (Box 654)
      - San Sebastiana 7/06/01 Flash, 2014-wa-16-0916; 1 (Box 654)
      - 07.01.2003 fotografie INNER LIGHT WITNESSES OF TIME di Flor Garduño, 2014-wa-16-0917; 1 (Box 654)
      - NICK BRANDT 34 PHOTOS 12/02, 2014-wa-16-0918; 1 (Box 654)
      - LIZ'S FILES BACKUP 8/12/05, 2014-wa-16-0919; 1 (Box 654)
      - Princeton's collection of the WHJ albums hshannon@princeton.edu, 2014-wa-16-0920; 1 (Box 654)
      - transact art COLLECTOR PASSPORT, 2014-wa-16-0921; 1 (Box 654)
      - NICK BRANDT 53 PHOTOS 03/04, 2014-wa-16-0922; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Backup #08 12/09/03, 2014-wa-16-0923; 1 (Box 654)
      - DMK cloud portfolio landscapes nudes Large Clouds State Pen, 2014-wa-16-0924; 1 (Box 654)
      - David Michael Kennedy Eight Northern Pueblos Portfolios, ENIPC Images, Lakota Dancers, 2014-wa-16-0925; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Back up #05, 2014-wa-16-0926; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Backup #07 09/26/03, 2014-wa-16-0927; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data 04 10/14/02, 2014-wa-16-0928; 1 (Box 654)
      - Peabody Essex Museum Curtis Copies 107 images, 2014-wa-16-0929; 1 (Box 654)
      - Joan Myers 982-9410, 2014-wa-16-0930; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Backup #06, 2014-wa-16-0931; 1 (Box 654)
      - Vroman, 2014-wa-16-0932; 1 (Box 654)
      - Peaboy Essex Museum Curtis Copies 107 images 1-9-01, 2014-wa-16-0933; 1 (Box 654)
      - System Folder Copy 10/18/00, 2014-wa-16-0934; 1 (Box 654)
      - VA/1091 (Hayden Album) Vol. 01 Disc 02, 2014-wa-16-0848; 1 (Box 654)
        General
        Unable to copy DVD.
  - James Horan research materials on the Civil War, Series X
    - James Horan, Timothy O'Sullivan Misc., 1965-1967 (Box 662)
    - James Horan, Timothy O'Sullivan Misc., 1965-1967 (Box 663)
    - James Horan, Timothy O'Sullivan Misc., 1965-1967 (Box 664)
    - James Horan, Matthew Brady Misc., 1887-1981 (Box 665)
    - James Horan, Matthew Brady Misc., 1887-1981 (Box 666)
    - James Horan, Matthew Brady Misc., 1887-1981 (Box 667)
    - James Horan, Matthew Brady Misc., 1887-1981 (Box 668)
    - James Horan, Timothy O'Sullivan copy prints, undated (Box 669)
    - James Horan, Timothy O'Sullivan copy prints, undated (Box 670)
    - James Horan Collection, Brady, inventory lists, 1981-2001 (Box 671)
    - James Horan Collection, Brady, inventory lists, 1981-2001 (Box 672)
    - James Horan Collection, Brady, inventory lists, 1981-2001 (Box 673)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., photographs, undated (Box 674)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., glass plates, undated (Box 675)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., glass plates, undated (Box 676)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., glass plates, undated (Box 677)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., glass plates, undated (Box 678)
    - James Horan, Brady, Misc., glass plates, undated (Box 679)
  - Books and serials, Series XI
    - Books and serials, 1990-2010 (Box A)
    - Books and serials, 1990-2010 (Box B)
    - Books and serials, 1964-2005 (Box C)
    - Books and serials, 2001-2011 (Box D)
    - Books and serials, 2001-2011 (Box E)
    - Books and serials, 1980-2010 (Box F)
    - Books and serials, 1980-2010 (Box G)
    - Books and serials, 1980-2010 (Box H)
    - Books and serials, 2000-2010 (Box I)
    - Books and serials, 1997-2010 (Box J)
    - Books and serials, 2000-2010 (Box K)
    - Books and serials, 1980-2000 (Box L)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box M)
      Includes Richard Rudisill.
    - Books and serials, undated (Box N)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box O)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box P)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box Q)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box R)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box S)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box T)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box U)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box V)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box W)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box X)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box Y)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box Z)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box AA)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box BB)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box CC)
    - Books and serials, undated (Box DD (Oversize))
    - Books and serials, undated (Box EE (Oversize))